# **Andrew Storrow**

Austin, TX 78704 • (585) 298-0076

andrew.storrow@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/andrew-storrow

Customer service oriented professional with 7 years of experience. Cultivates strong troubleshooting and communication skills with a high attention to detail. Recently obtained CompTIA A+ certification and seeking to transition into a career as an IT Support Specialist, Desktop Support Specialist, Help Desk Technician, IT Field Technician, or Field Service Technician.

#### **EDUCATION**

**CompTIA A+ Certification Training** 

Austin Community College

Austin, TX

Nov 2023

**Bachelor of Science, Software Engineering** 

Rochester Institute of Technology

Rochester, NY

## **SKILLS**

**Technology:** Software Troubleshooting • Hardware Installation • Peripheral devices • Mobile Devices • SOHO Networking

OS Installation • Data Backup • Security Techniques • Cloud, SaaS Solutions • Virtual Machines

Tools: Windows • Apple • iOS • Android • Command Line • Issue Tracking Software (Bugzilla, Monday) • Remote Desktop

Strengths: Problem Solving • Adaptability • Attention to Detail • Communication • Work Ethic • Dependability

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

El Famoso Austin, TX

eCommerce Fulfillment

Aug 2023 - Present

- Fulfill 300 customer orders a day while maintaining high quality and accuracy standards
- Effectively utilize ShipHero software on Apple iPads to manage workflow

Bonefide Productions Remote

Form Designer (Freelance)

Feb 2017 - Aug 2023

- Per month, updated dozens of PDF forms used as contracts by actors, artists and musicians to obtain work
- Leveraged advanced Adobe Acrobat functionality to create complex editable PDFs

**Stone Impressions** 

San Diego, CA

Production Team Member

Jun 2019 - Mar 2020

- Inspected hundreds of unique stone tiles daily to ensure quality for each customer's individual project
- Cultivated attention to visual detail in order to achieve accurate stone graphic printing using PhotoShop

## **Internal Revenue Service**

Austin, TX

Mail Processing Clerk (Seasonal)

Feb 2019 - May 2019

- Evaluated tax returns, correspondence and documents received in the mail
- Categorized and sorted over 200 items daily while adhering to detailed procedures

#### **Ascensus College Savings**

Newton, MA

Client Services Processor (Contract)

Nov 2016 - Feb 2017

- Processed hundreds of financial and account related transactions daily
- Utilized data entry software to efficiently manage processed transactions

### **Campaign For Vermont**

Remote

Technical Advisor

Feb 2016 - Nov 2016

- Published daily blog posts, email newsletters and Facebook ad campaigns for a grassroots organization
- Utilized NationBuilder software to manage a supporter database with thousands of members